Loretta Auma Khisa

Nairobi, Kenya.

+254723986615 loretta.khisa@umuzi.org lorettakhisa15@gmail.com https://www.github.com/lkhisa https://www.linkedin.com/Loretta-Khisa

ABOUT ME

Engineering graduate versed in reviewing plans, writing reports, researching solutions and implementing company procedures. I'm a vibrant, young and enthusiastic lady who is ready for new ventures in the field of electrical engineering and full stack web development.

SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS

- JavaScript
- Python
- HTML5 & CSS
- Electrical circuit technology
- Quality control and supervision
- Marketing

CERTIFICATES AND VOLUNTEER WORK

Volunteer

Do it With Boldness(DWB) Foundation 2020 - present.

Mentor, Google Cloud Track Google Africa Developer Scholarships 2021.

IT Automation With Python Certification Coursera December 2021.

Google Cloud Certification Google Africa Developer Scholarship February 12, 2021

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals, LGIT Smart Solutions June 19, 2020.

EXPERIENCE

Engineering Intern Kenya Revenue Authority January 2021 - December 2021

- Installation and maintenance of electrical equipment
- Servicing of lifts
- Inspection and repair of electrical sockets, lighting fixtures and electrical appliances
- Electrical wiring and cabling of newly constructed or partitioned office spaces.
- Preparing bill of quantities for technical projects.
- Consolidating reports of spending of the technical department.
- Preparing memos and mass emails for communication regarding planned projects of the technical department.

Back End Development Zuri and Ingressive for Good March 2021 - June 2021

- Back end development using python and Django
- · Peer code review
- Development of an ATM app project.
- · Development of a budget app project

Engineering Intern
Nairobi City Water and Sewerage Company
Itd

May 2019 - August 2019

- Networking equipment installation and maintenance
- Troubleshooting of networks
- Inspection and maintenance of electrical water pumps
- Electrical wiring and repair of sockets, lighting fixtures and electrical appliances.

Specialized Module on Cities and Climate Change United Nations Institute for Training and Research May 18, 2020

Climate Change
United Nations Institute for Training and Research
April 19, 2020

EDUCATION

Web Development Umuzi Academy September 2021 - Present

BSc in Electrical and Telecommunication Engineering Multimedia University of Kenya September 2015 - December 2020

High School Diploma Nakuru Girls High School January 2011 - December 2014

REFERENCES

Catherine Nyagah Officer, Lease Contracts and Assets Management, Kenya Revenue Authority. Catherine.nyagah@kra.go.ke

Geoffrey Rono
Assistant Manager, Lease Contracts and Asset
Management,
Kenya Revenue Authority
Geoffrey.rono@kra.go.ke

Winnie Ayieko
Chief Executive Director, DWB Foundation
winnieayieko@gmail.com